在可观测宇宙的边缘，时间尚未成形，空间尚未绷紧……
一团古老分子云，在引力微扰下开始自我聚拢……
核心温度攀升，压力激增——一场沉默的点燃正在酝酿。
但这一次，它没有点燃——质量越过临界阈值，光压溃败……
物质向内归零，空间向外震颤——黑洞初生。
从此，那里再无光逃逸，只有时空本身，记下了这一道皱褶。
This is the final descent across the black hole's boundary—light dragged, time stretched, space itself beginning to rotate.
You are crossing the matter critical zone—every gram of gas frictioning, radiating, and annihilating at near-light speed.
General relativity breaks down here… classical geometry dissolves, replaced only by the whisper of quantum fluctuations.
Scale collapses to zero—you’ve reached the smallest measurable unit of reality. Here, there is no 'position'—only the tide of probability.
Look—vacuum is not empty. It breathes. It sacrifices. And in doing so, radiates away this cosmic leviathan, slowly, silently.
Each flash erases a fragment of mass—a moment of entropy reversed, a thread of spacetime memory quietly unraveling…